<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Music and Sound Design</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Music and Sound Design</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© 2025 All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Youngcon - Music &amp; Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/1-yandex-youngcon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/1-yandex-youngcon/</guid>
      <description>Sound design and audio post-production for the official opening trailer of Young Con, Yandex&amp;rsquo;s premier IT and career festival. This high-energy video was utilized to launch the main stage program and set the tone for an audience exceeding 10,000 attendees. The focus of the sound design was to enhance the visual momentum and emphasize the scale and innovation of the tech conference. The project involved direct collaboration with the talented Yandex creative team to ensure seamless integration of sound and visual storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Gallet - Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/2-work-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/2-work-1/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration with Clim Studio. Created detailed sound design for product presentation, featuring delicate bottle textures, dynamic transitions, and subtle ambient elements that enhance the product&amp;rsquo;s aesthetic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UR TORUM- Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/2-ur-torum/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/2-ur-torum/</guid>
      <description>A pioneering exploration of high-production Russian Dark Fantasy animation, realized with cutting-edge AI technology. Directed by Dmitry Alekseev. Our team delivered a stunning auditory experience featuring Voice Over and a meticulous, immersive Sound Design. A benchmark fusion of modern tools and epic storytelling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Qatar - Music &amp; Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/2-yandex-beijing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/2-yandex-beijing/</guid>
      <description>Created a short intro video with phygital.team for Yandex presentation. Crafted a sound design blending modern composition with Eastern musical elements to highlight innovation and cultural depth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr Porter - Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/3-work-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/3-work-2/</guid>
      <description>Collaboration with Clim Studio. Created a winter-themed sound design for Mr Porter&amp;rsquo;s seasonal campaign, featuring crisp snow textures and atmospheric elements that enhance the winter aesthetic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aurora - Music &amp; Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/4-work-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/4-work-3/</guid>
      <description>Created original music and sound design for Aurora BR-X keyboard presentation. Developed a technical yet light sound palette that emphasizes innovation and precision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yandex - Music &amp; Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/8-work-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/8-work-7/</guid>
      <description>Created music and sound design for Yandex Practicum service. Developed a technical, light, and bright sound palette that reflects the educational platform&amp;rsquo;s innovative approach.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr Porter - Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/5-work-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/5-work-4/</guid>
      <description>Part of the Mr Porter series. Created space-themed sound effects that enhance the cosmic atmosphere, featuring ethereal textures and dynamic transitions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yandex Qatar - Music &amp; Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/2-yandex-qatar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/2-yandex-qatar/</guid>
      <description>Created a short intro video with phygital.team for Yandex presentation. Crafted a sound design blending modern composition with Eastern musical elements to highlight innovation and cultural depth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mr Porter - Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/6-work-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/6-work-5/</guid>
      <description>Another installment in the Mr Porter series. Created airy sound effects that convey lightness and space, enhancing the visual narrative through subtle sonic elements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Roger Gallet - Sound Design</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/works/7-work-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/works/7-work-6/</guid>
      <description>Continuation of the Roger Gallet series. Enhanced the product presentation with refined sound design elements that maintain brand consistency while introducing new sonic textures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alternative client for Splice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/splice-relationship/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/splice-relationship/</guid>
      <description>Personally, I have a weird relationship with Splice.&#xA;Sure, it&#39;s cool to have a tool that speeds up your workflow like that. But in the end, we still end up stuck in some kind of template, reusing the same one-shots over and over. That&#39;s why, over the years, I&#39;ve accumulated a ridiculous number of unused credits.&#xA;Buying entire sample packs just doesn&#39;t seem worth it to me.&#xA;Using melodic samples from Splice, in my opinion, is straight-up insane.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description> Let&#39;s Create Something Amazing Together! I&#39;m always excited to take on new and interesting projects. Whether you have a specific idea in mind or just want to explore possibilities, we&#39;d love to hear from you.&#xA;hihi@divosound.com @httpdivo @divo.divo.divo </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/links/</guid>
      <description> Connect With Me 👋Привет! Последний пост про Splice сможете найти у меня в телеграм канале!&#xA;PORTFOLIO TELEGRAM CHANNEL DM ME :) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
